# DEVDEEP BANERJEE

devdeep14.github.io/dportfolio

Game Designer

+91 9916267332



devdeep01@gmail.com



/devdeep-banerjee



github.com/devdeep14



#### PROFILE

Passionate designer, completed master's degree in Game Technology from ICAT Bangalore. Having 4+ years of working experience as a digital designer in web design and development, while working developed a keen eye for visual designs, graphics and programming. Seeking for an opportunity to work as a Game Designer having proficient knowledge in design documentation and user interface designs. Having hands-on experience on game engine tools such as Unity ProBuilder and Unreal.

# **EDUCATION**

MASTERS IN
GAME TECHNOLOGY (MSc)

ICAT Design & Media College 2021 - 2023

BACHELORS IN COMPUTER APPLICATION (BCA)

Bangalore University 2013 - 2016

Completed masters in game technology from ICAT Bangalore, affiliated to Alagappa University

Learnt the basics of game design challenges & development process along with game engines like Unity & Unreal with other 3D tools such as Maya and Substance

For final year project, designed an action-adventure FPS game with agent based sabotage missions in mountainous valley of India

Completed graduation in computer science from City College - Jayanagar, affiliated to Bangalore University

For final year project, created fully-functional insurance website which consists of purchase, claim & renew policy sections to manage user's account details

### WORK EXPERIENCE

**DIGITAL DESIGNER** 

Element14 Sept, 2019 - Sept, 2021 Part of Global Creative Services team, designing & developing complete marketing campaigns for element14 Asia-Pacific and clients based in Farnell EU & Newark NA

Creating form integrated landing pages & designing homepage leaderboard, supplier funded banners / product slots and merchandising eSpot banners

Brand reviewed marketing campaigns deployed across 42 sites in 26 languages, also worked in Adobe Target A/B testing for analyzing campaign results

**WEB & GRAPHICS DESIGNER** 

CRMIT Solutions July, 2017 - July, 2019 Designing, developing & maintaining company website along with creating marketing emailer campaigns and product landing pages

Creating visual imagery for company branding, creating corporate brochures, whitepapers, infographics and marketing slides

## COURSES & CERTIFICATIONS

#### • ULTIMATE GUIDE TO GAME DEVELOPMENT

Unity Technologies - Udemy 2022 - 2023

#### • COMPLETE C# UNITY GAME DEVELOPER 2D & 3D

GameDev.tv Team - Udemy 2022 - 2023

## SKILLS

- C / C++ / C#
- Unity Game Engine
- Unreal Game Engine
- HTML-CSS / Bootstrap
- Photoshop / Illustrator
- Adobe XD / Figma
- Maya / ProBuilder
- Substance 3D

# **KEY INTERESTS**

- Game Concept & Ideation
- Game Design & Visualization
- Visual Motion Graphics

## SOFT SKILLS

- Critical-thinking
- Strong analytical
- Problem solving abilities

## HOBBIES











